(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Donna decided to buy her two daughters water
bottles.
They were going to school soon.
She bought a pink one and a blue
one.
She drove back home.
Girls, I have something for you, her mom
yelled.
Sarah and Barbara ran to her.
What is it?
Sarah asked.
She showed them the water bottles.
They both grabbed the pink one.
They started pulling it.
I grabbed it first, Barbara said.
No, I did, Sarah argued.
The mom did not know what to do.
She thought one of them would like the
blue one.
She could just flip a coin.
One of them would still be mad though.
Donna decided not to give the water bottle
to any of them.